Good morning. I'm Hinano Okoshi, a 6th
grader of Nogizaka 46.
Where am I right now?
I'm at Miura Peninsula in Kanagawa
Prefecture.
Yay!
It's 5.30 a.m.
Look, I can only hear birds.
That's nice.
I'd like to try fishing for squids today.
Yay!
That's right. I used to go fishing with my
father in Shizuoka.
I will use that experience to catch a lot
of squids today.
I will do my best.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I can go fishing on a boat today, so I
will get on the boat.
I'm a little nervous.
Wow, I'm going to go. Thank you.
It's been a long time since I've been away
from the hustle and bustle of the city,
and I've come to a place surrounded by 360
degrees of nature, so I'm looking forward
to refreshing and having a lot of fun
today.
I feel like I've already gained something.
I wonder if this is the right way to say
it.
How should I say it?
My father's hobby is to enjoy fishing.
My grandfather's hobby is more serious.
My grandfather wakes up every morning.
In Shizuoka, there is a fishing village
called Numazu.
I went there early in the morning.
I was fishing while talking to my
acquaintances.
I was sitting next to it and I was
squeezing the net to put the boiled water
into the sea.
I was in charge of the boiled water.
This is a clutch.
If you use a clutch, you can get the
thread out if you lower it.
Please move it as big as possible.
I'm nervous.
What should I do?
I thought I might make a mistake.
I'm getting nervous about this electric
reel and the feeling of riding on this big
wave for the first time.
My heart is pounding right now.
I'll do my best.
I want to eat squid.
I can't go home without eating squid.
I'll do my best.
I'll stop the car.
I'm getting used to it.
It's quite heavy.
It's not heavy enough to hold the boat.
It's 100 meters deep, but it's still
light.
I'm fine.
You're fine.
I'm not going to cross the river.
It's very heavy.
I used to use a fishing rod for children,
but it was my first time using it because
it was not an electric rod.
But it's very fun.
It would be cool if I could use this.
I will do my best to master as much as I
can today.
I will fish from 80cm to the bottom.
How is it?
This is the first time I've caught a
squid.
I don't know the difference between the
pull of the fishing rod and the pull of
the wave.
Every time I catch a squid, I think I've
already caught a squid.
Isn't that the case?
Is this the weight of the wave?
It's still too early.
I'm still waiting.
I was sure I caught a squid earlier.
I was there.
I'm frustrated.
I can say anything.
I'm tired.
I will do my best.
I don't understand.
I still don't understand.
I used to go fishing in my hometown.
My father and grandfather, who love
fishing, were always next to me.
I never judged the fish I caught myself.
When I was told to give it to me, I
hurriedly gave it to me.
I hurriedly gave it to my father.
I remember the feeling of giving it to my
father.
Thank you for giving it to me.
I haven't caught anything yet.
The current location is the Miura
Peninsula, which you can see in the
background.
This is Chiba, the Boso Peninsula.
I saw Enoshima on the other side earlier,
but I couldn't see it.
I think there is Shizuoka in my hometown
on the left side of Enoshima.
I don't have a road in the sea, but I
think I can understand it.
I think there is something like a line
between the sea and the sea.
There is such a thing in the sea as well.
I was really interested in studying at
that time.
I hope I can take a boat someday.
I also want a boat.
If I can drive by myself, I can go by
myself.
It's strong.
It looks fun.
That's right.
But I don't want to twist it.
I don't want to twist it.
I'm going to make it the first Hina-no-
maru.
I'm planning to buy the second one.
There's no one.
This is a pose.
This is easy to catch.
I don't know.
This is said that if you want to catch it,
you can't catch it.
This is a cat-like squid.
Squid is a cat.
You should ignore it.
This is absolutely the case.
This is fast.
I thought this was absolutely the case.
My intuition tells me that this is the
correct answer.
I'm sorry.
I caught a fish.
I got the feeling of that time.
I thought I would definitely get a fish.
It was a mackerel.
It wasn't a mackerel.
This is light.
Even so, I don't know.
This is difficult.
I eat this.
I eat tuna on the sea.
Why is it so delicious to eat outside?
This is delicious.
I am proud of my achievements.
I caught a real squid.
I don't think there is a real squid.
This is dangerous.
I want to give up.
Please raise your hand.
I'm glad I did it.
I'm happy, but I don't have a good
feeling.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It may be amazing.
I may have pulled it up with a desperate
face.
I'm glad I caught it when I caught it.
I want to catch one more.
I will do my best.
This is cute.
Is there a fish?
I caught it.
I think this is the last spot.
I will do my best.
It's 108.
I raise it.
Which one is this?
Is this too much of a challenger?
How is it?
I feel like I have it.
I caught it.
I did it.
I will catch it.
This is the third time.
I'm sorry.
I will return it.
I'm glad I was able to catch it at the
end.
I'm happy.
I feel like I finally caught it at the
end.
I will do my best not to forget this
feeling today.
I want to master it.
I will return to the land.
It's been a long time since I've been to
the land.
So I came back from the dock.
Thank you very much.
And this squid seems to be able to be
processed on this ship.
I will try to eat it after processing it.
I will peel the skin first.
I'll cut it and leave it for a while.
I cut it open and cut it like sashimi.
I eat it with soy sauce and wasabi in the
car on my way home.
I just cut it.
Please don't say that it's a lot.
I will dip it in soy sauce and eat it.
This is delicious.
This is sweet.
This is fresh and sweet.
This is very sweet.
This is delicious because I caught it
myself.
This is delicious.
I'm glad I did my best.
I will grill this.
This looks delicious.
This is squid.
This is mayonnaise.
This is mayonnaise soy sauce.
Can I use mayonnaise soy sauce?
I will win.
This is fun.
I eat this.
Where should I eat this?
I eat the main body.
I eat this.
This is a beautiful brown color.
I eat this in one bite.
Is this hot?
I eat this.
This is delicious.
This is hot.
This is 100 points.
I'll have soy sauce and mayonnaise.
This is the first place in the squid
category.
Squid is the first place in the squid
I think we are used to that kind of
balance.
This is amazing and delicious.
I was looking forward to this today.
I'm happy to be able to eat squid that I
caught, grilled, and sashimi.
I think I'm the happiest person in the
world right now.
I had time to eat squid.
Thank you very much.
I want to do this many times with such a
wonderful project and location.
I'm looking for people who like to hide.
I want to invite various people.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to my channel and give it
a high rating.
See you.